A Guide to the Massey-Faulkner Collection
University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library, #6271-j
Massey-Faulkner Collection 1949-1956
University of Virginia. Library. Special Collections Dept. Alderman Library University of Virginia Charlottesville, Virginia 22903 USA
6271-j
ca. 309 items
Linton Massey
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
A gift of Mr. Massey on 7 December 1963, but not accessioned until 22 January 1964.
Container List
- Manuscripts
  - Manuscripts of Linton Massey's "Notes on the Unrevised Galleys of Faulkner's Sanctuary, " AMs 81 p. on 75 l., TMs 30 p. on 30 l., [1956]; AMs & TMs revised
  - "Notes on the Unrevised Galley's of Faulkner's Sanctuary ", [1956]; Galleys, 6 p. on 6 l.
- Correspondence
  - Correspondence of Kenneth Godfrey and Linton Massey, 1955; 5 ALS, TLS, w/env, 1 calling card; 7 items
  - Richard S. MacCarteney to N. Harvey Deal, 1955 Apr 1; TL, 2 p. on 1 l.
- Miscellaneous
  - Note cards on the unrevised galley's of Faulkner's Sanctuary, 1955-1956; Note cards, 75 items
  - Press notices and letters of congratulations on Linton Massey's "Note on the Unrevised Galley's of Faulkner's Sanctuary ", 1956; Press notices & correspondence; 16 items
  - Receipts and invoices re: purchases and services for the Massey-Faulkner collection, 1949 Mar 23-1959 Dec 1; Receipts & invoices; 208 items
- Photograph
  - William Faulkner before Hadrian's Tomb in Rome. Duplicates photo #0086-a, [1955]; Photo; neg w/print